<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pattaya Tour</string>

    <!-- Labels for the drawer items -->
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="get_here">Getting Here</string>
    <string name="shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="accommodations">Lodging</string>
    <string name="family_activity">Family Fun</string>
    <string name="adult_activity">Adult Fun</string>
    <string name="nav_header">Pattaya Thailand</string>

    <!-- Info tab for all categories -->
    <string name="information">Info</string>

    <!-- Welcome message -->
    <string name="welcome_message">Welcome to Thailand, the Land of Smiles.\n
        \nWe will be going on an adventure to Pattaya City, located in the
        Chonburi Province south of Bangkok. \n \nSo buckle up it\'s going
        to be a wild ride, or something like that.</string>

    <!-- Welcome string activity_main -->
    <string name="welcome_thai">ยินดีต้อนรับ</string>
    <string name="welcome_english">(Welcome)</string>

    <!-- Welcome Warning -->
    <string name="warning_warning">Warning!!!</string>

    <!-- Warning message for Adult Section -->
    <string name="warning">The Adult Fun section is information on Pattaya\'s sex industry. This may not be for everyone. So, if
    you\'re homophobic or just a frigid person in general you might want to avoid this section. Otherwise ENJOY!!!</string>

    <!-- Airport Tabs -->
    <string name="airport">Airport</string>
    <string name="taxis">Taxi</string>
    <string name="bus">Bus</string>

    <!-- AirportPageAdapter -->
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="web_site">Web Site</string>

    <!-- Airports -->
    <string name="suvarnabhumi">Suvarnabhumi</string>
    <string name="donmueang">Don Mueang</string>
    <string name="utapao">Utapao</string>
    <string name="all_airports">All Airports</string>

    <!-- Airport Cities -->
    <string name="bangkok">Bangkok</string>
    <string name="rayong">Rayong</string>

    <!-- Airport Bus -->
    <string name="bell_travel">Bell Travel</string>
    <string name="bus_ekamai">Ekamai Terminal</string>

    <!-- Airport Taxis -->
    <string name="bangkok_taxi">Bangkok Taxi24</string>
    <string name="smile_taxi">Smile Taxi Service</string>

    <!--  Airport Web Sites -->
    <string name="web_utapao">http://www.utapao.com</string>
    <string name="web_airports_bkk">http://www.airportthai.co.th</string>
    <string name="web_bell_travel">http://www.belltravelservice.com</string>
    <string name="web_ekamai">http://www.busonlineticket.co.th</string>
    <string name="web_smile_taxi">http://www.smiletaxiservice.com</string>
    <string name="web_bkk_taxi">http://huahin.bangkoktaxi24.com</string>

    <!-- Airport information message headers -->
    <string name="airport_info_airports_header">Airports:</string>
    <string name="airport_info_taxi_header">Taxis:</string>
    <string name="airport_info_bus_header">Buses:</string>

    <string name="airport_info_airport_text">Suvarnabuhmi is Thailands biggest and main airport. It is located on the
    south end of Bangkok going towards Pattaya, which is convenient for our purpose. \n\n I have never had any issues coming
    through any of the airports on the list. If you have your arrival card filled out in advance, then you should not have
    any problems. Customs is also a breeze, if you aren\'t an idiot. \n\nWhat I really like about Suvarnabuhmi is that all
    transportation is easy to get to. For taxis and buses, just go down to level 1 from the arrivals level (level 2), and
    there they are. \nI don\'t know a whole lot about the other airports because I never took a taxi or a bus from either
    one. However, the buses and taxis are pretty much the same everywhere in Thailand.</string>

    <string name="airport_info_taxi_text">From level 1 you can get a taxi to Pattaya or the Ekamai Bus Terminal. There are taxis,
    vip limos and vans to choose from. It all depends on your budget. \n\nIt all depends on what kind of time you have and what
    your budget is. A taxi to Pattaya from Suvarnabuhmi will cost about 1,500 baht. One from Don Mueang will cost about 2,000
    baht. and one from Utapao will cost around 1,000 baht.</string>

    <string name="airport_info_bus_text">You can also go down one more level and take the train into Bangkok then
    get off at the end of the line (Phayatai Station), get on the Sky Train. Take the Sky Train to Ekamai and there\'s the bus
    station. \n\nThe bus from the airport is about 160 baht I think, but they don\'t run 24 hours. \n\nThe Ekamai way by using the airport
    train and Sky Train will cost about 250 baht total, however, this is the slowest route and the last bus is at 10 or 11 p.m. \n\n
    </string>

    <!-- shopping_list_item xml -->
    <string name="shopping_center">Shopping Center</string>
    <string name="shopping_location">Location</string>
    <string name="shopping_description">Description</string>

    <!-- Shopping Tab -->
    <string name="shopping_tab">Shopping</string>

    <!-- Shopping Centers -->
    <string name="avenue">The Avenue Mall</string>
    <string name="big_c_extra">Big C Extra</string>
    <string name="central">Central Festival Mall</string>
    <string name="central_center">Central Center Mall</string>
    <string name="floating_market">Floating Market</string>
    <string name="harbor_mall">Harbor Mall</string>
    <string name="mikes">Mike Shopping Mall</string>
    <string name="night_bazaar">Night Bazaar</string>
    <string name="night_market">Night Market</string>
    <string name="outlet_mall">Outlet Mall</string>
    <string name="spacer"> </string>
    <string name="royal_garden">Royal Garden Mall</string>
    <string name="terminal">Terminal 21 Mall - Coming Soon</string>
    <string name="tukcom">IT City</string>

    <!-- Shopping Center Locations -->
    <string name="second_rd">Second Road</string>
    <string name="central_rd">Pattaya Klang</string>
    <string name="beach_rd">Beach Road</string>
    <string name="sukhumvit">Sukhumvit Road to Rayong</string>
    <string name="thepprasit_rd">Thepprasit Road</string>
    <string name="outlet_rd">Sukhumvit and Thepprasit Intersection</string>
    <string name="pattaya_north">Pattaya North and Second Road</string>
    <string name="pattaya_south">Pattaya South Road</string>

    <!-- Shopping Information -->
    <string name="shopping_info">There\'s a lot of shopping in and around Pattaya. We have so many malls and markets, you can
    find pretty much anything you are looking for. Not just the malls, but there are tons of little shops that have different
    items in them. \n\nThe markets are everywhere, depending on what day it is. There are several day markets and then you have
    the night ones. \n\nThepprasit is probably the biggest and well known night markets. It is open on Thursday through Sunday.
    \n\nThe malls are open everyday. Of course, nothing really opens here until 10 or 11 in the morning, so make sure to check
    the times. \n\nIn the malls the stores are name brand and of good quality just like anywhere else in the world. Of course,
    the same cannot be said for the smaller shops and markets. You get what you pay for. \n\nWe also have a lot of grocery stores
    in case you are staying for a long time. We have a great bulk item store Makro. \n\nEnjoy shopping!! \n</string>

    <!-- Shopping Center Descriptions -->
    <string name="avenue_description">The Avenue has some small shops, a gym and a very well stocked grocery store Villa Market mainly
    catering to foreigners with foreign food.</string>

    <string name="big_c_extra_description">Big C Extra is comparable to a Walmart super store. They have food and other things.
    There is also a hardware store like Home Depot, food court and restaurants.</string>

    <string name="central_description">Central is the biggest mall in Pattaya at this time. It has six floors with brand name,
    high end shopping, a bowling alley, awesome movie theatre, two floors of restaurants, a food court, banks.</string>

    <string name="central_center_description">Central Center has a Big C similar to Big C Extra. It has just received a
    makeover, and is improved. It has a movie theatre, resuarants, and stores. The Hilton sits on top of the mall.</string>

    <string name="floating_description">The Floating Market is outside of town going towards Rayong. It is a big tourist
    attraction as it hosts local made crafts and souvenirs. Plenty of resaurants too. Sometimes it\'s a bit crowded with
    all the bus tours.</string>

    <string name="harbor_description">Harbor Pattaya is finally something for kids. It has some shopping, resaurants, a food
    court. The biggest attractions are for kids. They have Harbor Land which is a big soft play area, ice skating, wall climbing,
    snow land, roller land, trampoline jumping, an arcade, different schools. It was a long time coming, we needed it.</string>

    <string name="mike_description">Mike\'s has been around for a long time. It has some outlet type shopping. Mostly tourist
    stuff inside. It\'s like four floors of shopping, a few places to eat. That\'s about it.</string>

    <string name="night_bazaar_description">A huge area with tourist trinkets.</string>

    <string name="night_market_description">The night market on Thepprasit is a big and crowded place. It has very good deals
    on clothes. There is a whole section for food, which is very good. It\'s crowded but worth the trip.</string>

    <string name="outlet_description">The Outlet Mall is next to the night market. The mall has great deals on brand name clothes,
    shoes and some other stuff.</string>

    <string name="royal_description">Royal Garden Mall is one of the oldest malls here. It has a movie theatre, resuarants,
    shopping, and Ripley\'s. I stayed here when it was Royal Garden hotel in \'85. Hehehe</string>

    <string name="terminal_description">Our soon to be newest mall. It will have plenty of shopping. Not sure what else will
    be in there.</string>

    <string name="tukcom_description">Tukcom or IT City is where you go for all your IT needs. It has everything you could
    need. Banks, phones, lots of phones, computers, cctv cameras. There is a floor for gaming, videos, music and software for 
    very cheap. You can get Xbox360 games for 100 baht.</string>

    <!-- Shopping Web sites -->
    <string name="avenue_web">https://pattayasanook.com/pattaya-avenue-shopping-mall/</string>
    <string name="big_c_extra_web">https://pattayasanook.com/big-c-extra/</string>
    <string name="central_web">http://www.centralfestival.co.th/index.php</string>
    <string name="central_center_web">https://pattayasanook.com/central-center-pattaya/</string>
    <string name="floating_web">http://www.pattayafloatingmarket.com/</string>
    <string name="mikes_web">http://www.mikeshoppingmall.com/</string>
    <string name="night_bazaar_web">http://www.pattayanightbazaar.com/</string>
    <string name="night_market_web">https://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g293919-d4554040-Reviews-Thepprasit_Road_Nightmarket-Pattaya_Chonburi_Province.html</string>
    <string name="outlet_web">http://www.outletmallthailand.com/our_branch/1</string>
    <string name="royal_web">http://thailand-explored.com/royal-garden-plaza-pattaya/</string>
    <string name="terminal_web">http://www.terminal21.co.th/pattaya/th/home/</string>
    <string name="tukcom_web">https://www.facebook.com/TukcomNews</string>

    <!-- Lodging and Hotels -->
    <string name="hotel_tab">Hotels</string>

    <string name="lodging_info">There are hundreds of hotels and rooms available in Pattaya. They all offer amenities that
   you would expect from other hotel in the world. Thais are very service oriented people and take great pride in providing
   the best quality of customer care. \n\nThere are five star hotels and cheap rooms. It all depends on what you want to do
   and what you are here for. Pretty much all mid-range rooms offer great amenities, like a pool, safe in the room to mention
   a few. Also most hotels have safety deposit boxes available at the front desk. \n\nI use Agoda.com to book all of my rooms.
   I have found that you can usually add a star to most of the rooms they have listed. I have yet to have a bad time or a bad
   room using Agoda. \n\nTip: If you are nice to the staff and ask questions and not demand, you will get better service and
   upgrades. I worked in the hotel industry, and it\'s easy to give someone that \"attitude\" room that overlooks the garbage
   cans. \n\nHere are a few hotels that are available. All of these are close to the beach or on the beach and in the middle
   of the excitement. \n\nNot to worry if you don\'t make a reservation, there are plenty of rooms for walk-ins. \n\n</string>

    <!-- Lodging Web Sites -->
    <string name="hilton_web">http://www3.hilton.com/en/hotels/thailand/hilton-pattaya-BKKHPHI/index.html?WT.mc_id=zELWAKN0APAC1HI2DMH3LocalSearch4DGGenericx6BKKHPHI</string>
    <string name="hard_rock_web">http://pattaya.hardrockhotels.net/</string>
    <string name="flipper_web">https://www.flipperhotels.com/flipper_house/</string>
    <string name="nautical_web">http://www.nauticalinn.co.th/home/index.php?lang=en</string>
    <string name="queen_vic_web">http://www.queenvicpattaya.com/</string>

    <!-- Family Activity -->
    <string name="family_tab">Family</string>
    <string name="family_activity_activity">Activity</string>
    <string name="family_location">Activity Location</string>
    <string name="family_description">Activity Description</string>

    <string name="family_info">There’s a lot of activities for families to do in and around Pattaya. We have indoor and outdoor
    activities the whole family can enjoy. There\'s something for everyone in the family, from water parks to elephant rides.
    Pattaya and the Chonburi province have some of the most interesting and unique attractions for families to visit. \n\nThere
    is always something going on in Pattaya. There are a couple marathons during the year, a huge music festival and fireworks
    competition held every year. Not to mention our Songkran Festival runs after the rest of the country and is very popular with
    locals and tourists alike. \n\nIn addition to the mainland tourist attractions, there are 10 islands not to be missed:
    \nKoh Larn (Coral Island) \nKoh Phai \nKoh Si Chang \nKoh Samet \nKoh Sak \nKoh Rin \nKoh Krok \nKoh Talu
    \nKoh Khram \nand Koh Klet Kaew (The Monkey Island) \n\nSo no matter what you want to do, I\'m sure there is something here
    for the whole family to enjoy. \n\n</string>

    <!-- Family Activity Activities -->
    <string name="cartoon_activity">Cartoon Network Amazone</string>
    <string name="elephant_activity">Elephant Village</string>
    <string name="gocart_activity">Go Cart Racing</string>
    <string name="harbor_activity">Harbor Land</string>
    <string name="khao_kheow_activity">Khao Kheow Open Zoo</string>
    <string name="nong_nooch_activity">Nong Nooch Gardens</string>
    <string name="parasail_activity">Parasailing</string>
    <string name="ramanyana_activity">Ramanyana Water Park</string>
    <string name="sanctuary_activity">Sanctuary of Truth</string>
    <string name="tiger_activity">SriRacha Tiger Zoo</string>

    <!-- Family Activities Locations -->
    <string name="cartoon_location">15 kilometers from Pattaya</string>
    <string name="elephant_location">About 20 minutes from Pattaya</string>
    <string name="gocart_location">Thepprasit Road Pattaya</string>
    <string name="harbor_location">Inside Harbor Mall on Central Pattaya</string>
    <string name="khao_kheow_location">About an hour from Pattaya</string>
    <string name="nong_nooch_location">16 kilometers from Pattaya</string>
    <string name="parasail_location">Beach Road Pattay</string>
    <string name="ramanyana_location">20 kilometers from Pattaya</string>
    <string name="sanctuary_location">Bang Lamung Pattaya</string>
    <string name="tiger_location">About 30 minutes from Pattaya</string>

    <string name="cartoon_description">Cartoon Network Amazone is centered around the Cartoon Network with it\'s
    characters. The water park is nice and there are a lot of slides there. The kids area is nice and big, good for little kids.
    It is a little pricey though. It\'s an all day event.</string>

    <string name="elephant_description">Elephant Village is a nice place to visit. It is also an elephant sanctuary. Go visit
    their web site. It is something you don\'t want to miss.</string>

    <string name="gocart_description">The go carts are good fun. Of course, it is for the older kids and not really the young ones.
    There are more than one go cart track here so it\'s not boring with the same track.</string>

    <string name="harbor_family_description">Harbor Pattaya is a great place for kids of all ages. It\'s right in town and very
    accessible. They have ice skating, roller skating, wall climbing, trampolines and of course the big padded Harbor Land.
    It was great to see it open, there wasn\'t much for kids before.</string>

    <string name="khao_kheow_description">The Khao Kheow open zoo is great fun. This is a little ways from Pattaya, but it\'s
    worth the trip. It\'s an open zoo, so you have to drive around or walk a lot. Don\'t worry, there is transportation
    available in the zoo. It\' an all day event.</string>

    <string name="nong_nooch_description">Nong Nooch Gardens is a fun place to go. They have different shows and you can ride
    an elephant there if you want to. There are several tours going there, or you can go on your own. It\'s an all day event.
    </string>

    <string name="parasail_description">Parasailing is all over the beach. You just have to go out to the beach in the morning
    and you\'ll see all the people waiting to take you out to parasail. You can see several people doing it from the beach every
    morning. It\'s n early morning thing. It\'s in town and close to convenient.</string>

    <string name="ramanyana_description">Rmanyana is the newest water park in Thailand. It is big and has a lot of slides. It is
    a little journey from town though. But not to worry there are plenty of cars and buses going out there. It is in the
    Silver Lake area which has the Big Golden Buddha on the mountain, a winery and other stuff. This is an all day event.</string>

    <string name="sanctuary_description">The Sanctuary of Truth is a wonderful temple. This was and is still being built all by
    hand. There are several craftsmen working on different projects. They do not use any power tools to carve the pieces and they
    are all joined together with special cuts and workmanship. No power tools an no nails used in the construction. This is a
    must see. It\'s in town so it\'s close.</string>

    <string name="tiger_description">The Sriracha Tiger Zoo is a nice place. They have several shows with tigers, elephants and
    crocodiles. It\'s a pretty big park, so a lot of walking. This is also an all day event.</string>

    <!-- Family Web Sites -->
    <string name="cartoon_web">https://www.cartoonnetworkamazone.com/</string>
    <string name="elephant_web">http://www.elephant-village-pattaya.com/</string>
    <string name="gocart_web">http://www.pattayakart.com/en/</string>
    <string name="harbor_web">https://www.harborpattaya.com/</string>
    <string name="khao_kheow_web">http://www.khaokheow.zoothailand.org/</string>
    <string name="non_nooch_web">http://www.nongnoochtropicalgarden.com/</string>
    <string name="parasailing_web">http://pattayaguide.org/pattaya-parasailing-pattaya-guide</string>
    <string name="ramanyana_web">https://www.ramayanawaterpark.com/</string>
    <string name="sanctuary_web">http://www.sanctuaryoftruth.com/</string>
    <string name="tiger_zoo_web">http://www.tigerzoo.com/eng/</string>

    <!-- Adult Tabs -->
    <string name="soi">Soi</string>
    <string name="penthouse">Penthouse</string>
    <string name="lgbt">LGBT</string>

    <!-- All Adult Information Tab -->
    <string name="adult_info_header">What Happens Here Stays Here</string>

    <string name="adult_information">Let\'s be honest. Sex sells, everything from candy to cars. \n\nThis will be a journey
    through Pattaya\'s thriving adult entertainment playground. \n\nGet ready to be offended or learn something new about yourself. As
    the girls say, \"You never know if you never try.\" \n\nA few things you need to think about before we begin. This is Thailand,
    not your country. So, what\'s acceptable here may not be acceptable there and vice versa. Most foreigners don\'t understand Asia
    and Asian culture until you\'ve experienced it first hand. Sex is a business for them and they treat it that way. \n\nLadyboys
    - Let\'s talk about Thailand\'s third gender: Ladyboys. Ladyboys can be found in every facet of Thai society. \n\nA Ladyboy
    is a transexual male who is either pre-op or post-op, it doesn\'t matter, they are still referred to as she or her. \nIt\'s
    not always easy to tell a Ladyboy from a Girl-Girl. If she\'s too beautiful, then she\'s probably a Ladyboy.
    \n\nWalking Street - Walking street is one of the biggest attractions in Pattaya.
    It\'s located at the south end of Beach Rd., and is closed to vehicle traffic at 7 p.m. every night because it comes alive
    at night. \n\nIt has go-go bars, discos, restaurants, hotels and everything else you may be looking for. \n\nOf course if you\'re
    really feeling dirty, you can always go get a soapy massage. \n\n\"The bars are temples but the pearls \nain\'t free - You\'ll
    find a god in every golden cloister - And if you\'re lucky then the god\'s a she - I can feel an angel sliding up to me\"
    \nOne Night in Bangkok - Murray Head.\n\n</string>

    <!-- Adult Activities -->
    <string name="soi_six">Soi 6</string>
    <string name="soi_seven">Soi 7</string>
    <string name="soi_eight">Soi 8</string>
    <string name="soi_bukhao">Soi Bukhao</string>
    <string name="soi_walking_street">Walking Street</string>
    <string name="boyz_town">Boyz Town</string>
    <string name="penthouse_hotel">Penthouse Hotel</string>
    <string name="adult_soi_text_view">Soi</string>
    <string name="adult_sexes_text_view">Sexes</string>
    <string name="adult_description_text_view">Description</string>
    <string name="sexes_one">Workers: Ladies - Ladyboys</string>
    <string name="sexes_two">Workers: Ladies - Ladyboys - Gay Men</string>
    <string name="sexes_three">Workers: Men - Gay Men</string>
    <string name="ladyboys">Ladyboys</string>
    <string name="everywhere">Located Everywhere</string>
    <string name="tiffany">Tiffany\'s</string>
    <string name="tiffany_caberet">Ladyboy Caberet</string>

    <!-- Adult Fun Soi Descriptions -->
    <string name="soi_six_description">There are a lot of girl-girl bars as well as a number of Ladyboy bars. Typically,
    the girls working here are \"Farm Fresh\" and still have mud between their toes. They are still learning. Then they
    will go over to another Soi, a Beer Garden or Walking Street. This is known as a short time Soi and most bars have rooms
    upstairs.</string>

    <string name="other_sois">General Soi. They have open air beer bars, some go-go bars.</string>
    <string name="soi_boyz_description">This has a lot of gay bars as well as straight bars for the ladies.</string>
    <string name="walking_street_description">This is the major tourist area. There is something for everyone\'s taste.
    You can find go-go bars, discos, Ladyboys, girls, foreign girls, gay men, lesbians, couples, groups. Pretty much whatever you\'re
    looking for and can afford, you can find it here.</string>

    <!-- Penthouse description -->
    <string name="penthouse_description">The Penthouse is a boutique hotel that caters to all. It exists so you can live out
    your greatest desires or fantasies. It sits across from Boyz Town and just down the street from Walking Street. This hotel
    has a joiner fee, but only after the first two people. This means you can bring back two people, any gender
    and there is no charge, if you bring three, there is a 500 baht charge for the third person and so on. It\'s an awesome hotel.
    It has a cave design, and very sound proof, you don\'t hear any of your neighbors. \n</string>

    <!-- Adult Websites -->
    <string name="walking_street_web">http://www.bangkok.com/pattaya/nightlife/walking-street-back-up.htm</string>
    <string name="soi_six_web">https://soi-6.com/s/bars/bars-part-1/</string>
    <string name="soi_seven_web">https://lovepattayathailand.com/soi-7-pattaya/</string>
    <string name="soi_eight_web">http://pattayaguide.org/soi-7-and-8-pattaya</string>
    <string name="penthouse_web">https://www.penthousehotel.com/</string>
    <string name="tiffany_web">http://www.tiffany-show.co.th/</string>
    <string name="boyztown_web">http://gaybuttonthai.com/viewtopic.php?t=5908</string>
    <string name="ladyboy_web">https://katoeys-are-us.com/</string>
    <string name="soi_bhukhao_web">http://www.pattaya-adventures.com/soi-buakhao.html</string>

</resources>
